ideas-shared.com 2013-10-11

# Ideas-Shared | Empowers You To Get Direct Action, Investment, Knowledge And Public Support!

This privacy policy governs the collection, storage and use of personal information collected by us, Internet-Shared Limited, via the Website Ideas-Shared.Com. It provides you with details about the personal information we collect from you, how we use your personal information and your rights to control personal information we hold about you.  

Please read this privacy policy carefully: by accessing the Ideas-Shared.Com Website, or ordering any item from us, you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this privacy policy in its entirety. If you do not agree to this privacy policy in its entirety, you must not use the Website. If you have any questions relating to this privacy policy, please contact us at CUSTOMERCARE@INTERNET-SHARED.COM   

**Who we are**  

The Website is operated by Internet-Shared Limited ("Internet-Shared"), a company registered in England and Wales with company number 07380070.  
In this privacy policy, "we" "us" "our" and "ideas-shared" mean Internet-Shared and "you" and "your" means the individual accessing the Website. We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal information you provide to us in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and other applicable privacy laws.  
If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use personal information, or if you have any other privacy related questions, please contact us by any of the following means:   

e-mail us at CUSTOMERCARE@INTERNET-SHARED.COM or 

write to us at:

Internet-Shared  
67 Lyon Road  
Crowthorne  
RG45 6RX  

**A quick word about children**  

We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any unsupervised child under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may not use the Website unless you have the consent of, and are supervised by, a parent or guardian.  

**The personal information we collect about you  
**

When you access and use the Website (including when you submit personal information to us through the registration process or elsewhere within the Website), we may collect the following information from you:  

  * your email address;
  * your postal address;
  * your mobile telephone number;
  * your payment details, for example, your credit or debit card details.  

**How we may store and use your information**  

We (or third party data processors acting on our behalf, such as PayPal Limited) may collect, store and use your personal information listed above for the following purposes:  

  * to register you with our Website, make the Website available to you and to administer the Website;
  * to provide you with services that you request;
  * to enable us to process and deliver your order for an item;
  * for assessment and analysis purposes, for example, customer and product analysis, to enable us to review, develop and improve our services; and/or  

Please note that the personal information you give us in relation to an on-line sale is obligatory, necessary for recording and processing the delivery of your order, as well as for the billing team. You have the right to access, modify or correct the information given. To exert this right, you should contact our Customer Service team.  

We will give you the opportunity to opt in to receive marketing information by e-mail from us and we will only send it to you if you do opt in or if you are an existing customer and the information relates to similar items or services to those which you have previously purchased from us. When we send you communications by e-mail, we will give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving such communications from us. It is not our normal practice to send out marketing communications by post or telephone but if we do, you will be able to opt out of receiving such communications from us. However, remember if you opt out of receiving communications from us, particularly by email, that this will preclude you from receiving our special offers or promotions in future.  

We will not disclose, sell or rent your personal information to any third party unless you have consented to this. If you do consent to receive marketing information from us or carefully selected third parties but later change your mind, you may contact us by email at any time at customercare@internet-shared.com and we will cease any such activity.  

If a third party acquires all (or substantially all) of our business and/or assets, we may disclose your personal information to that third party in connection with the acquisition. We may also disclose your personal information where we are required to do so by applicable law, by a governmental body or by a law enforcement agency.  

Finally, we may also collect anonymous details about users of our Website for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. Certain pages of the Website can sometimes contain electronic images or statistics trackers, which make it possible to count the number of visitors to the page. This can be used with certain partners in order to measure and improve the effectiveness of certain adverts. The information obtained is anonymous and simply makes it possible to gather statistics on the frequency of use of certain pages of the Website. No single individual will be identifiable from the anonymous details we collect for these purposes.  

**Cookies**  

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser. If you wish, you can usually adjust your browser so that your computer does not accept cookies. We do not exchange cookies with any third party websites or external data suppliers. The only cookies we use are related to each connection and are deleted at the end of each visit of the Website.  

**International transfers**  

We will not transfer any personal information relating to you to any country outside of the European Economic Area, without your consent.  

**Security**  

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal information that you provide to us, no transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any personal information that you transfer over the Internet to us.  

**Your rights**  

You have the following rights:   

  * the right to ask us to provide you with copies of personal information that we hold about you at any time, subject to a fee specified by law; 
  * the right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information that we hold about you free of charge; 
  * the right to opt out of any marketing communications that we (or any third party to whom we have disclosed your personal information with your consent) may send you.   

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please contact us at customercare@internet-shared.com.  

**Third party sites**  

Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal information that we collect and we cannot be responsible for personal information that third parties may collect, store and use through their websites. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.
